Eduardo Campos-Sanchez

Chicago, IL

ecamposchez10@gmail.com

Detail-oriented with 3+ years of customer service experience and a background in sales. Communicative, self-starter, adaptable, and disciplined in maintaining the highest standard and integrity. Often referred by individuals to assist with technical issues whether in the workplace environment or daily personal use. I am dedicated to bringing my background experience and merging it with IT, Software Development, and Engineering. Motivated to learn HTML, CSS, JS, and Python with the assistance of school and boot camps.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer Apprentice

Discovery Partners Institute - Chicago, IL February 2023 to Present

Apprentice at DPI

Key Holder/Sales Associate

Ashley Furniture HomeStore - Chicago, IL June 2021 to September 2021

Assisted in disposing store waste

Assisted with customer issues in a timely and comforting manner

Assisted with associate overrides whenever needed

Assisted with polishing the company store

Assisted contacting guest for colleagues as well as following up

Able to stand in prolonged periods

Exceptional Customer Service

Assisted colleagues with sales and split sales

Able to work for long hours

Reviewed emails for proper and professional format

Motivated the team to provide overall better store statistics

Team player

Being comfortable leading and providing leadership

Obtained a 10% increase in sales each month

Fulfillment Expert

Target - Chicago, IL

September 2020 to May 2021

Be courteous at all times

Be efficient and precise

Adapted and provided excellent customer service

Personally chose to acquire knowledge on the company store to provide better customer service In learning the store I provided a 20-40% increase in productivity

Learned department in less than a month/ Quick learner Assisted colleagues and was a team player

Crew Member

McDonald's - Chicago, IL June 2019 to May 2020

Be courteous to customers at all times
Provide precise and efficient service
Earned up to \$30 from recognition
Guest demanded to provide myself tips due to my exceptional service
Worked well under pressure in a fast paced environment

Education

BC in Software Development

City Colleges of Chicago-Harold Washington College - Chicago, IL January 2022 to Present

High school diploma in Business and Finance

Aspira Business and Finance High School - Chicago, IL August 2016 to June 2020

Skills

- Sales
- Leadership
- Customer service
- HTML5
- CSS
- Python
- Ruby
- GitHub
- · Ruby on Rails

Languages

- English Fluent
- Spanish Fluent

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/eddy10/

Sales skills — Proficient

May 2021

Influencing and negotiating with customers

Full results: Proficient

Customer focus & orientation — Highly Proficient

May 2021

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity

Full results: Highly Proficient

Real estate — **Expert**

May 2021

Matching listings with specifications

Full results: Expert

Verbal communication — Proficient

May 2021

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.